bellroy.com 2018-08-23

# Customer Care: Shipping, Delivery, Warranty & Exchanges | Bellroy

## Estimated Arrival Time

Where would you like to ship to? 

Choose Destination 

We’ve worked hard to simplify the delivery of bags and minimize the cost of shipping for you. If you have any questions about the options above, reach out to support@bellroy.com.

## Worldwide Shipping

Bellroy customers live all across the globe, so we can ship to anywhere with a letterbox. For P.O. boxes outside Australia and Europe, please use the regular shipping option at checkout (our team of trained delivery owls aren’t allowed in government buildings just yet).

We usually dispatch orders within 2 working days. Delivery times vary based on selected service and destination. Regular post ranges from 3 to 28 working days depending on the shipping address. For more accurate shipping windows check out our Estimated Arrival Time Calculator above.

## Express Shipping

We offer express delivery to most locations with tracking available. Express shipping is generally 1–3 working days for the US, UK and Australia, and anywhere from 2–8 working days for other countries. If you live down a kangaroo trail in Kalkarindji, please allow a bit of extra time.

​In a few locations around the world we don’t offer an express option. This is because the current express services in those regions aren’t reliable enough, or there are currently no options available in that region. 

For pricing and more detailed timeframes please use our Estimated Arrival Date Calculator above.

## Customs Fees

Extra duties and taxes may apply to the following regions: Asia, South America, Africa and some European countries that are not members of the EU. During the checkout process a pop up will appear for applicable countries once the shipping destination has been selected. If you’d like to find out more please [email our support team](mailto:support@bellroy.com).

## Returns

We’re pretty stringent with our quality control, but occasionally something might slip through the cracks. If your product is faulty, or we sent you an incorrect order by mistake, send it back to us within 60 days of delivery for a full refund (including shipping*).

If you change your mind (it happens to the best of us), or wish to return an unwanted gift, we will still refund your purchase if returned within 60 days, but the return shipping isn’t covered and refunds will be sent to the original purchaser’s method of payment. All items must be returned in original condition and in the original Bellroy packaging.

Remember, all our products come with a 3 year warranty, so if something goes awry down the track, be sure to let our support team know via [support@bellroy.com](mailto:support@bellroy.com). 

*If you are eligible, we’ll email a prepaid returns slip to you.

## Exchanges

If you change your mind, or want to swap a gift for something else, exchange requests can be submitted to [support@bellroy.com](mailto:support@bellroy.com) within 60 days of purchase. 

Please return your item in original condition, and in the original Bellroy packaging. We recommend using regular post – take a photo of your returning package with the postage receipt visible so we can ship your preferred product without delay. 

If you made an error when purchasing online, and it’s still within 48 hours of placing your order, contact our support team right away and we should be able to adjust your order before it leaves our hands. We like to reduce unnecessary shipping (and save you unnecessary costs) where possible.

## Order Tracking

All express shipped orders can be tracked online. However, not all regular shipments have this option. You can find your tracking number two ways:

  1. Check the shipping confirmation email we sent you (this should arrive in your inbox within 48 hours of purchase). The email will contain a tracking link if there’s one available.

If that doesn’t work:

  2. [Email our support team](mailto:support@bellroy.com) and quote your order number/customer reference number. We’ll help you with the rest.

## What if my order doesn’t arrive?

If your order doesn’t arrive within the maximum estimated timeframe we’ll send out a replacement using express shipping wherever it’s available. Simply [email our support team](mailto:support@bellroy.com) with your order details.

## How do I cancel my order?

Contact [support@bellroy.com](mailto:support@bellroy.com) within 24–48hrs of placing your order. That way we should be able to catch any transaction settlement and shipping before it goes through. Anything after this window will be treated as a regular refund.

## Can I add items to my order after I have hit the place order/confirmation button?

If you want to add an item to your order please [email our support team](mailto:support@bellroy.com) within 24hrs of your purchase and we’ll do what we can to adjust things.

## What are my payment options?

We happily accept Mastercard, Visa or Paypal.

## What currency can I pay in?

Depending on where you're browsing from, we try to select the best currency for you to pay in. All transactions are processed in the currency shown on the product and checkout pages. Most countries have tax included in the price, if not, the tax will be shown on the checkout page before purchase.

Our products are covered by a 3 year warranty from the day they were bought, when used under normal conditions and for the purpose intended. Try not to over stuff your Bellroy or put things in there that don’t belong (like ninja stars). If you do put more cards in there than recommended, things can stretch out of shape and put undue stress on the stitching and other materials.

This warranty covers faults in materials and workmanship and doesn't apply if damage is caused by unreasonable use or neglect, normal wear and tear, or if you change your mind. 

In order to make a warranty claim, you need to have purchased your Bellroy through our website or one of our authorized re-sellers.

The Bellroy warranty sits alongside applicable consumer protection law.

##  How do I make a claim? 

Please [email our support team](mailto:support@bellroy.com) with your order details and a description of the fault or damage. Including photographs of any fault helps a lot in speeding up claims.

## Where are Bellroy products designed?

The design process mostly happens in our Bells Beach office in Australia, where we have a gifted team of people from all over the world. The Bells office is equipped with a design lab that lets us prototype new styles using 3D printing, laser cutting and other fun design toys. Occasionally our team works with external designers in places like the USA to collaborate on special projects. This helps keep things fresh, with new ideas and techniques flowing through our HQ on a regular basis.

## Where are Bellroy products made?

We’re committed to working with the most talented people we can find around the world, no matter where they’re from. Currently, makers in China and India offer the best balance of quality workmanship and value we’ve been able to source, so this is where all of our products come to life.

We recognize there can be concerns when manufacturing in these regions, so all of our major suppliers must comply with a Supplier Code of Conduct. We also work closely with each supplier to ensure staff are treated well and that environmental and social responsibilities are taken seriously. You can find some of our broader thoughts on Responsible Business here.

## How will my purchase be packaged?

We have custom-made cardboard envelopes for every product which you can see in the final image on each product page. 

## How many cards do the products fit?

For each Bellroy style, we let you know the number of cards it can hold on the product page. This is always a range and is included in the features list located just under ‘Add to Cart’. You can see we recommend 4–11 cards for our Note Sleeve, for example.

## Are all the wallets as slim as each other?

No. Within our range, some are slimmer than others. Essentially, the more features you want (e.g. access to lots of cards with equal priority), the more storage space you'll need to accommodate that. Check out Slim Your Wallet and find out which wallet is best you.

## Are Bellroy wallets the slimmest? 

No. We do not have the slimmest wallets. If you want to wrap your cards in cling film, you can make a slimmer wallet. Instead, what we offer is a wallet that is as slim as we can get it without compromising on intelligent interactions, considered materials, and comfort in everyday use.

## Where can I find the Micro Pen available with some of your products?

That cute little pen is called a Walkie Pen. Unfortunately, we don’t currently sell them separately. It’s likely you’ll be able to purchase one online. Search for the name “Walkie Pen” and options to buy should pop right up. You can also purchase the cartridge refills, which are titled “Pilot BRF-8F 0.7”

## Are Bellroy products RFID protected?

We appreciate that theft using RFID skimming can happen in certain circumstances, so we’ve made our [Note Sleeve](http://bellroy.com/products/note-sleeve-wallet/leather_rfid/black), [Hide & Seek](https://bellroy.com/products/hide-and-seek-wallet/hi_rfid/black) and [Travel Wallet](http://bellroy.com/products/travel-wallet/leather_rfid/black) RFID secure. The technology has been incorporated into these styles as this is where we believe the technology will be most useful, but please let us know if we should consider the technology for other Bellroy products by emailing us [support@bellroy.com](mailto:support@bellroy.com)

## What is RFID Protection? 

RFID-blocking wallets are designed to help protect you from a specific type of theft, called RFID skimming – which is where information from high frequency (13.56MHz) RFID-based credit cards, passports and transport passes are read and duplicated. RFID skimming is not common, but it can happen in certain cases. For a more detailed article on RFID we recommend [this balanced explanation by our friends at Carryology](http://www.carryology.com/bags/a-quick-guide-to-rfid-security/).

Our number one environmental goal is to make products that are used and loved for as long as possible. So, our materials need to be robust and maintain a lasting appeal.

## Our Leathers

Premium leather is durable, supple and has timeless appeal. It ages gracefully and forms a unique character depending on how you use it. This makes it ideal for wallets and other small carry goods. Despite extensive ongoing research, we’re yet to find another material that offers the same balance of qualities (eg most faux or vegan leathers perform poorly when it comes to environmental impact or long term durability). 

All of our leathers come from [Gold Rated LWG tanneries](http://www.carryology.com/liking/industry/introducing-leather-working-group/), which helps ensure its production meets strict environmental guidelines. To read more about considerations in this space, including animal welfare concerns, please read our page on Responsible Business.

If you’re interested in the different types of leather we use, how it ages and how to care for it, check out Our Leather page.

## Our Complementary Materials

In our phone cases we combine leather with moulded thermoplastic polymers to provide extra protection and durability over the life of the products. The inside of most of our cases are lined with microfibre to cushion your phone and help avoid scratching your precious device.

In select All-Conditions product we offer a 500 denier woven polyamide with a double polyurethane backing. It is lightweight, while providing solid abrasion and water resistance for secure protection from the elements.

All zippers we use are premium YKK zips, including the YKK Aquaguard zipper for All-Conditions styles.

Other linings we use are recyclable polyester. Threads are nylon. Both offer long term durability (and therefore improved environmental impact) over other cotton options we’ve tested.

As our product range grows, so does the range of materials we use to produce them. We aim to update this section over time as things develop.

We would love the world to be a better place because of Bellroy, and we know that responsible business can help us get there.

We're proud to be part of the [B Corp movement](http://bcorporation.com.au/community/bellroy) – a group of certified companies using the power of business to help solve social and environmental problems. Because this is what drives us, we’ve stamped it into our mission:

Promote better ways to carry.   
Use business as a force for good.   
Help the world, and our crew, flourish.

You can read more detail about our social, environmental and animal welfare considerations here.

## Customer Support

If you've bought a Bellroy product and it hasn't performed to expectations, or if you want to know more about the brand, send our support team a message. They like nothing more than making people smile and given half a chance will partake in some playful banter.

You can email us at [support@bellroy.com](mailto:support@bellroy.com)

## Sales

If you're a retailer who would like to stock Bellroy, please email our sales team with the following information: Store Name, Address, Website, Photos of Your Shop, 3 other brands you currently carry: [support@bellroy.com](mailto:support@bellroy.com)

## Press

If you'd like any further information, high resolution images, or would just like to say hi: [press@bellroy.com](mailto:support@bellroy.com)

## Communities

We like to think that there is always a way for you to stay engaged and up to date with the latest Bellroy news. Visit our Bellroy [Facebook](http://facebook.com/carryBellroy), [Twitter](http://twitter.com/bellroy) and [Instagram](http://instagram.com/bellroy), otherwise try our Carryology [Facebook](http://facebook.com/carryology), [Twitter](http://twitter.com/carryology) and [Instagram](http://instagram.com/carryology).

We offer 24-hour customer support 7 days a week. You can contact us via: 

  * Live chat

We’re a small, knowledgeable and enthusiastic team of people eager to answer your questions and solve your Bellroy problems, no matter what time of the day or night. 

We do this via multiple digital channels, but we don’t offer phone support for the following reasons: 

  * We wouldn’t be able to offer the same level of support over the phone, as we often need to share photos of products or screen shots of the website with our customers. Email, facebook and live chat are best for this reason.
  * We can instantly check your order status or solve an issue via live chat without needing to put you on hold.
  * We’re a global support team. Our current channels allow us to use translators so that we can effectively communicate with all of the members in our community.
  * Using online support channels allows us to keep your information and support history in the one spot, making sure that we have a detailed account of our communication with you. Nobody likes having to explain a situation over again because you get a different support person when you call. 

If you have any further questions please contact us via support@bellroy.com or one of our other channels. 

Welcome to bellroy.com (the 'Site'). Here are some details about how we work.

Please review the following basic terms that govern your use of and purchase of products from our Site. Please note that your continued use of our Site constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by these terms.

### 1\. Currency and Pricing

All transactions are processed in the currency shown on the product and checkout pages. Most countries have tax included in the price; if not, the tax will be shown on the checkout page before purchase.

### 2\. Shipping and Delivery

Bellroy delivers products to most of planet earth and select parts of our solar system. Shipping rates are outlined on our Shipping page, and will be quoted with any order.

### 3\. Customer Service

Bellroy is committed to providing exceptional customer service and quality products. Standard dispatch timeframes are between 1–3 business days. If you have any questions or concerns about a product, your order, or life in general, [email our support team](mailto:support@bellroy.com).

### 4\. Return Policy

Bellroy assists with easy returns to make sure you're happy with your purchase.

Our products all have a 3 year warranty, so if anything isn't as it should be get in touch and we'll sort out an exchange or refund straight away.

If you've made an error in purchasing, don't hesitate to ask our team for advice. The earlier we catch things, the more chance we have of reducing unnecessary shipping, which is kinder to the environment. Even better, choose as carefully as you can before hitting that confirmation button of joy. Hurrah.

### 5\. Warranty

Bellroy products are covered by a 3 year warranty. Full details are here.

### 6\. Copyright

The contents of our website, and the site as a whole, are intended solely for personal, noncommercial (other than for the purchase of merchandise from our Site) use by its users.

You may download or copy the contents and other downloadable materials displayed on bellroy.com for your personal use only. No right, title or interest in any downloaded materials is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading or copying.

You may not reproduce (except as noted above), publish, transmit, distribute, display, modify, create derivative works of, sell or participate in any sale of, or exploit in any way, in whole or in part, any of the contents of this site.

### 7\. Security

When purchasing from Bellroy your financial details are passed through a secure server using the latest 256-bit SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption technology. 256-bit SSL encryption is the current industry standard. If you have any questions regarding our security policy, please [email our support team](mailto:support@bellroy.com).

Effective Date: 25 May 2018

### Introduction

### 

Bellroy takes privacy seriously – we are committed to keeping your personal information private. All personal data we collect is kept strictly secured, and is only used for the purposes described in this privacy policy.

This privacy policy applies to information collected through our websites and any information we collect offline (for example, if you talk to our customer services team).

### Who are ‘we’?

When we talk about “we” (or “our” or “us”), we mean Bellroy Pty Ltd and all its wholly owned subsidiaries. We are based in Australia but we supply goods all over the world.When we talk about “we” (or “our” or “us”), we mean Bellroy Pty Ltd and all its wholly owned subsidiaries. We are based in Australia but we supply goods all over the world.

We also store backups of some data, including order details (which will include Customer Information) on our servers in Australia. We use appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect the personal data that we collect and process. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal data, including using the latest 256-bit SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption technology to protect your Customer Information when you purchase from our online store. Bellroy also complies with the [Australian Privacy Principles](https://www.oaic.gov.au/privacy-law/privacy-act/australian-privacy-principles) in relation to the proper use and storage of personal data.

>

For European Union data protection purposes, when we act as a controller in relation to your personal data, Samuel Giles is our representative in the European Union. You can contact him on [eu-privacy@bellroy.co.uk](mailto:eu-privacy@bellroy.co.uk)

### What is ‘personal data’

Personal data is any data that could directly or indirectly identify you – this includes information like your name, address, telephone number and your email address but in some cases it may include less obviously identifying information, like your IP Address (see below).

### What data do we collect

When you visit bellroy.com or shop with us online, we collect information about you and your use of our website. We treat this information as falling into three categories: Customer Information, Usage Data and your IP Address.

Customer Information is the information you explicitly provide to us when you make an online purchase or sign up to receive our newsletters, including your:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Shipping and/or billing address
  * Payment information

**Usage Data** is general information about how you interact with our website, such as:

  * which pages you visited on our website
  * how you came to the website (for example, by clicking on a link in a newsletter or from an advertisement)
  * which buttons or links you clicked
  * whether you have been to the website before

Whenever you visit a website (including ours), the computer from which the web pages are served (i.e. our web server) needs to know your computer’s public network address so it can send the requested pages to your browser. The public network address associated with your computer is called its “public **IP Address** ” and is sent automatically each time you access any Internet website. From a computer’s IP Address, it is usually possible to determine the general geographic location of that computer but often not the specific computer and if multiple people use the computer not the specific user (although if your IP Address is unique to you and is published somewhere or if you later identify yourself while while using the same IP Address, it is possible that IP Address could identify you).

In the European Union, your IP Address is considered to be personal data, and we treat it accordingly.

### How we collect data

**Information you provide to us directly:** When you shop with us online, we will ask you to provide personal data (such as your name and address) so we can fill your order. We may also ask you to provide personal data when you sign up for a newsletter, respond to a job application or an offer, join us on social media, take part in surveys or contact us for help. If you don’t want to provide personal data, you don’t have to, but it might limit your ability to do certain things on the website.

**Information we collect automatically:** When you visit bellroy.com or shop with us online, we collect some information about you automatically, including Usage Data.

Some of this information is collected using cookies or other similar tracking technologies that have been placed by us or by third parties. For details of how cookies work, which ones we use and how you can control them, please see our [cookie policy](https://bellroy.com/customer-care#cookie-policy).

### How we use data

Where we collect your personal data, we’ll only process it:

  * to fill orders placed by you, or
  * where we have legitimate interests to process the personal data and our interests are not overridden by your rights, or
  * in accordance with a legal obligation, or
  * where we have your explicit consent.

The main reason we use your personal data is to fill orders and to manage our relationship with you (for example, dealing with questions about products, returns and warranty claims).

We also use personal data for other purposes, including:

**To communicate with you:** this may include providing you with information you’ve requested or that we’re required to provide to you, that relates to changes to our website or policies, marketing communications in accordance with your preferences or to invite you to provide feedback or to take part in research we are conducting.

**To support you:** this may include dealing with any questions you have about our products, dealing with warranty claims or any issues relating to our goods or services.

**To improve our website:** we use Usage Data to help us understand the online behaviour of our customers, which helps us to focus our marketing activities and improve the services we provide on the website. Using web analytics on our website enables us to measure, collect, analyse and report on Usage Data for the purposes of understanding and optimising customers’ experiences on our website. We try to ensure that all Usage Data is anonymised (i.e. not referable to a specific person) unless we have your consent.

Geographical location information contained in Usage Data also enables us to tailor your experience on our website by displaying different content based on your location, such as providing content in your preferred language (where possible), showing local currency and pricing, and showing relevant advertising. Again, geographical location information is anonymised unless we have your consent.

**To protect you:** we use Customer Information and your IP Address to detect and prevent fraudulent activity when you want to make a purchase from us.

**To market to you:** we use Usage Data for remarketing (sometimes called retargeting) to better target our ads to interested customers. Retargeting uses cookies to identify visitors who visit a certain website and then doing something with that information, such as showing a particular brand of goods or services on other websites. So, after you have visited our website, you (or another user of your computer) may see Bellroy ads on certain participating third party websites, such as on the Google Display Network and Facebook. This will only occur if you have agreed to us using non-essential cookies.

**To analyse, aggregate and report:** we may use the personal data we collect about you and other users of our website to produce aggregated and anonymised analytics and reports, which we may share with third parties.

### How we can share your personal data (and how we don’t)

There will be times when we need to share your personal data with third parties. We will only disclose your personal data to:

  * handle payments securely (PayPal Inc and Braintree Payment Solutions LLC)
  * distribute direct marketing materials that you have consented to receive (MailChimp)
  * connect to social networks (for example, Pinterest, Facebook, Instagram and LinkedIn)
  * pay commission to affiliates
  * target advertising (for example, Google, Facebook)
  * protect you and us against fraud (for example, MaxMind)

There also may be times when we are legally required to disclose personal data, such as to regulators, law enforcement bodies, government agencies, courts or other third parties where we think it’s necessary to comply with applicable laws and regulations, or to exercise our legal rights. Where possible and appropriate, we will notify you of this kind of disclosure.

We only share your Customer Information with third parties where it is either necessary to enable online transactions (such as PayPal) or where you have consented to receive direct marketing material (such as MailChimp).

Your personal data is never disclosed to third parties for remarketing or retargeting purposes. Bellroy never sells its email lists or customer information.

### International data transfers

When we collect, process and share data in accordance with this privacy policy, it may be transferred to countries other than where you live. Our data hosting provider’s servers are located in the United States, and many of the third parties with whom we share data are also located in the United States.

When we do transfer data, we will make sure that there are safeguards in place to protect your personal data.

For individuals in the European Union (EU), this means that your personal data will be transferred outside of the EU. EU personal data will only be transferred to countries that have been identified as providing adequate protection for EU data (such as New Zealand) or to a third party where we have approved transfer mechanisms in place – this means that we have either entered into an appropriate Data Processing Agreement or by ensuring that the entity has appropriate data protection in place, including where the entity is [Privacy Shield](http://www.privacyshield.com/welcome) certified (for US-based third parties).

We also store backups of some data, including order details (which will include Customer Information) on our servers in Australia. We use appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect the personal data that we collect and process. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal data, including using the latest 256-bit SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption technology to protect your Customer Information when you purchase from our online store. Bellroy also complies with the [Australian Privacy Principles](https://www.oaic.gov.au/privacy-law/privacy-act/australian-privacy-principles) in relation to the proper use and storage of personal data.

### Retention

How long we retain your personal data depends on what it is, what we need it for (for example, keeping track of your warranty rights) and whether we are legally required to keep it (for example, for tax). Once we no longer need to retain it, we will make sure your personal data is deleted or anonymised.

### Your rights

Your personal data belongs to you, and you have the right to:

  * know what personal data we hold about you
  * make sure that all personal data is correct and up-to-date
  * ask us to correct any personal data
  * object to our continued processing of your personal data

If you no longer wish to receive any online communications, just let us know by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of the newsletter or other communication.

You can notify us if you no longer wish us to process your personal data, but we not that if you do so, this may mean that we can no longer provide our services to you.

You can contact us at any time by emailing [privacy@bellroy.com](mailto:privacy@bellroy.com) or, if you are in the EU, email [eu-privacy@bellroy.co.uk](mailto:eu-privacy@bellroy.co.uk) and we will respond to your request within one month.

If you have any complaints or concerns about how we manage your personal data, please contact us by emailing [privacy@bellroy.com](mailto:privacy@bellroy.com). If you are in the European Union, you also have the right to complain to your local [Data Protection Authority](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/reform/what-are-data-protection-authorities-dpas_en) about the collection and use of your Personal Data.

For details of how to manage cookies, see our [cookie policy](https://bellroy.com/customer-care#cookie-policy)

### Changes to this Policy

We may revise this privacy policy from time to time as we add new features or as laws change. When we make changes to our privacy policy, they are reflected on this page and the a revision date will be noted at the top. Any revised privacy policy will apply to personal data, Customer Information and Usage Data we already have about you at the time of the change, and any such information created or received after the change takes effect. We strongly recommend that you periodically reread this privacy policy to see if there have been any changes that may affect you.

### How to contact us

You can contact us by emailing [privacy@bellroy.com](mailto:privacy@bellroy.com) or, if you are in the EU, [eu-privacy@bellroy.co.uk](mailto:eu-privacy@bellroy.co.uk)

Bellroy Pty Ltd  
5 Theatre Place  
Canterbury  
Victoria 3126  
Australia

Last revised: 25 May 2018

### What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small text file that is set in your browser when you visit a website, and which may assign an anonymous identifier to you.

### What cookies/tracking technologies do we use?

There are a few different types of cookies that we and some of our affiliates and third-party service providers may use: persistent cookies (that stay on your hard drive until removed) and session ID cookies (that automatically expire after a period of time, or when you close your browser).

There are also other tracking technologies that may be used, such as web beacons and local storage. Web beacons allow us to monitor site behaviour by delivering your IP address, any cookies we may have set and information about the page you’re visiting to a server. We use local storage to keep track of your preferences, things you've seen, temporary personal identifiers and more; the data we store in local storage generally stays on your device.

### Why do we use cookies/tracking technologies?

We use cookies (and other tracking technologies – but for ease, let’s just call them cookies) for lots of reasons: they let us customise your experience (for example, seeing prices in the correct currency), operate the website (like enabling you to put things in your cart and then keep shopping) and generally make sure that your experience of our website is a good one. We also use cookies to perform analytics and deliver advertising or marketing that is relevant to you.

There are also cookies set by third parties that allow us to provide interactive content, perform analytics and enable other third party features, like payment or links to social media.

### How can you control cookies?

You can control cookies by amending your web browser controls. You can also delete existing cookies from your web browser and/or disabling cookies on your computer and other devices. Depending on the particular browser you are using (for example, Google Chrome, Safari, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox), this can usually be done by accessing the ‘Browsing History’ through the ‘Settings’ or ‘Options’ menu (or equivalent) in your web browser, or if you are using a different device, then in the ‘Settings’ for that device.

Some cookies are essential to the proper operation of our website: if you disable cookies in your web browser, or delete existing cookies, our website may not work properly and your experience with our website will be less personalised and may make your shopping experience less enjoyable.

It is important to remember that if you delete existing cookies but do not disable cookies in your web browser, and then you subsequently visit our (or any) website, fresh cookies may be placed and you may need to repeat the process of deleting existing cookies.

You can also opt out of targeted advertising: see <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> or [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

You can also alter your ad preference settings on Google, Facebook and other third parties, and on the platforms of other providers.

Finally, if you do opt out of receiving communications directly from us, we will no longer use your information for those purposes.

### Do Not Track

Some browsers allow you to automatically notify websites that you visit not to track you by using a ‘Do Not Track’ signal. If you have Do Not Track enabled when you visit our website, we will treat that as you having rejected cookies and not place any cookies other than those essential to the proper functioning of our website.

### Additional cookie information for those who want to know more

1\. We have two ways of collecting location information, both of which preserve your anonymity – either we use only the first three octets of your IP Address for a rough location that can sometimes be wrong, or we use a browser-based Geolocation API which can only work with your explicit consent to non-essential cookies (your browser will pop up a dialog asking for your consent).

2\. Even if you reject cookies, after visiting our website you may notice that you see more Bellroy ads on other websites. This is probably because you have provided consent (even if you didn’t mean to) somewhere along the line to a third party, such as Google or AdWords, who may notice that you have visited the Bellroy website.

3\. We use (anonymous) session IDs every time you visit our website. These are essential to ensure the website works properly, but it also means that you may be served some pages (such as product recommendations) based on usage data. The session ID is not linked to any personal data and cannot be used to identify you.

4\. When you place an order or sign-up to our newsletter or otherwise provide personal data, that will be linked to your session ID and the information we have collected so far (and that until then was anonymised). You can ask us to “unlink” this information at any time by emailing us at [privacy@bellroy.com](mailto:privacy@bellroy.com) or [eu-privacy@bellroy.co.uk](mailto:eu-privacy@bellroy.co.uk)
